So y'all know that I'm not feeling festive this year at all.
There's an entire genocide taking place
in several parts of the world,
one of which we're literally watching every day
on our phones and we can't seem to do anything to stop it.
Nonetheless, we also cannot seem to stop my mother
from coming up with a Christmas tree theme every year.
This is specifically, specially, and Christmas-ly
for you, the SEAL Squad.
Now I know we have a lot of new members, so welcome.
This is something that we do every year.
Are we religious?
No, but we are Christmas, so we will decorate,
we will do all the things.
Last year's theme was the crown.
It is time for the annual unveiling of Nettie's Christmas tree.
So without further ado, Annette first tell us
where did the idea for this year's tree come from
before we reveal the actual theme.
Happy holidays, everybody.
This is Nettie.
Only happening at TheAmandaverse.com
where all the cool kids hang.
Well, at least the ones that just really like my stuff.
See you there.